

Denys Ordynskyi PRODUCT DESIGNER

5+ years of UX/UI design experience of digital products

Ukraine, Kyiv <u>denisordyskyi@gmail.com</u> **Skype: ordik_ghk** https://ua.linkedin.com/in/dennieo

Summary

Forward thinking, detail and usability oriented product designer designer. Great team player, passionate about creating trendy and user-friendly experiences for customers around the world.

Self-motivated and quick to learn individual, like to take ownership over the tasks, love to ask right questions, and able to write HTML 5 / CSS 3 code + (light JS).

Experience

December 2014 - January 2016

Senior UI / UX Designer at www.chatbox.com

Here i was on duty for the look and feel of the product.

June - December 2014

UI/UX Designer at **Bilberry Software** (5 months)

Worked on several products: www.trackolade.com and Internal Reports for Chipotle Chain.

2014 - now

UI/UX Designer at **Blue Stout** (over 1 year)

Freelancing at NYC digital agency. Cover several really cool projects like: www.interact.com, www.trupoly.com

From 2012

Freelance as **UI/UX Designer**

Behind i have

- 5+ years of UX/UI design experience of digital products
- Master of design tools: Sketch, Adobe CC, pen and paper, whiteboard and dryerase markers
- Able to create prototypes in: Framer, Pixate, HTML/CSS/JS

- Strong visual design skills and background designing for systems (style guides, design patterns)
- Ability to generate pixel-perfect assets
- Strong knowledge of front end technologies to communicate effectively with engineers
- Able to write HTML 5 / CSS 3 code
- Experience in ecommerce
- Experience in one page web application
- Passion for anything design

APPLICATION DETAILS

Cover Letter

Hey, i'm Denys from Kyiv (Ukraine).

i'm 29 have a great family - my wife and my daughter (cat and dog lover:) Working as UI UX Designer last 5 years, working on iMac / Macbook pro and fluent with Adobe CC suite, Sketch3 (prefer it more), like using invisionapp for prototyping and collaborating.

I start lear coding HTML / CSS / JS this summer (Treehouse / codecademy) and always open to new information, read design relative blogs, watching videos and of course deep thinking person.

Before this i worked in 7 years Tourism field in positions: CMO, CEO and know how business works, and understand many business tips.

You may ask why i'm here as UI / UX designer?

I'm just loving this, love solve problems and help users. Design is my passion, really.

This starts when i hear our team was really unhappy using our internal app when i was CMO. Than i want to help them by improving user experience using my feelings and our 2 devs:) and i fall in love in this. And than this made design my hobby, and after that hobby became my work.

Here is some of my works:

https://dribbble.com/usabillla - not too much - more things under NDA, sorry. And i did't do fake designs for posting.

https://www.acinteract.com

www.chatbox.com

www.centralpark.com - soon will be published updated version (Really proud i made UI & UX for the greatest park - heart of NYC).

http://uxcheckup.com

http://cpwdentistry.com

https://www.trupoly.com

http://rubinmuseum.org

Education

2002 - 2007

Specialist Faculty of Tourism, Hotel and Restaurant Business at **Kyiv University of Tourism, Economics and Law**

I will be pleased to talk with you via skype: ordik_ghk email gehucka@gmail.com phone +380504431720 Dennie.